The world, what a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
seize it, raise your flag, and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless everlasting
world out there.
I know that with the
burning passion driving me.
Someday, somewhere, I'll
finally see the light!
I have searched for everywhere.
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart.
I know that
has been
hiding has opened up
its doors for me to
go and
though
I travel.
Far from where my search began.
Over seas of green and shores of sand.
Through the endless
everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Some days where I'll
finally see the light.
I will search for everywhere.
Look at them!
How are they still standing?
Ah, yeah!
Bellamy, wipe the floor with
that clean-haired freak!
This town ain't for no dreaming, cowards!
Show that pansy the meaning of pain!
What's all the commotion about?
I heard Bellamy's pirates are
holding a lynching in there.
Luffy! Zoro!
Why are you letting
them beat you like that?
Go ahead and fight back!
You guys can take them no problem!
it's no use lady they're
too smart for that
they've obviously come
to the realization that
they're way out of
their league refusing to
fight a stronger opponent
it's disgraceful but
it is smart clearly the
runt lacks any dignity
as a captain the marines sure are generous
these days to be willing
to fork over 30 million
for the head of a
worthless smart mouth child
Zoro, no matter what
happens, don't fight back.
Come on, fight back.
Sounds nice, huh?
The doctrine of non-resistance.
So, you're weak and you have no pride.
You refuse to get into a fight.
And your head is swimming
with silly daydreams.
They sound like children.
More like little girls.
My work here is done.
When I heard a bounty
worth 30 mil was in town,
I wondered what kind of a
badass crook came with it.
Needless to say, I'm more
than a little let down.
I'm bored with these cowards.
Quick, get them out of my face.
Bye, ladies.
Luffy, let's get them
all over like a genius.
Luffy.
Zoro!
Hey. Sweet thing.
If you keep hanging out with these
losers, you're gonna get left behind.
Especially when the new era rolls around.
What if I bought you?
You seem like a simple girl.
You can't fetch too high of a price.
Excuse me?
Did you say you wanna buy me?
That's right. Come on, girl.
Join us.
I hate to say it, but I'm too good
to be seen with a pirate like you.
You're nothing but a small-time thug.
I like your attitude!
I've never seen the twins before my life!
Take your two friends and get out of
my sight before I decide otherwise.
You got that, weakling?
Don't ever show your face in here again!
The Sky Island does exist.
That place really does
make a killer cherry pie.
Got something you want to say?
Now what could you
possibly be angry about?
Your two friends won that fight
without even throwing a punch.
Huh, you think you'll surpass us?
When next we meet, we'll
both be top pirates.
I respected the way you
treated them back there.
You got nerves of steel, lady.
Luffy!
This new era they keep rambling
on and on about is a load of crap.
The era when pirates dream of
treasure will come to an end.
Yeah right.
What are you talking about?
The dreams of pirates.
Will never end.
Am I right?
For somebody shouting as loud as you
are, you sure are talking nonsense.
What are you talking about dreaming for?
One-upping your peers isn't easy.
What's with you?
Did you melt your brain?
I wonder what all the commotion is about.
Forget it.
Those losers are probably
taking out their frustrations.
They can laugh at us all they
want because when you aim high
you often come across fights
that just aren't worth fighting!
Right.
Let's go.
Luffy?
Oh, it looks like I interrupted you.
Are you in a hurry, kid?
One more thing.
I hope you find your way to Sky Island.
Maybe we should keep talking to him.
He may know something about Sky Island.
Who was he?
I don't know.
And it's not he.
Huh?
If it's not he, then what is it?
Probably they. Come on, let's go.
What do you mean, they?
Are you saying there were others with him?
Where?
I didn't see anyone.
Hello, are you even listening?
It's a beautiful day for a bottle of rum!
Board! Board!
Board!
Seriously I know I say this all the time
but one thing I am not
is a ship repair man.
But you're really good at doing this sort
of thing osap I know it's quite amazing
I'm incredibly Versatile I say we trash
this and buy a new ship instead are you out
of your mind do you have any Idea how we
got our hands on this ship yeah yeah I've
heard it a thousand times it was given to
by the most gorgeous girl in your village,
right?
Who cares?
It's just plain dangerous to keep
relying on a ship in this condition.
That's why I'm repairing it, idiot!
Now get down here and give us
a hand! Repairs, huh? This?
It won't hold.
Bipe me! Ha-ha!
That face is hilarious, Zeus!
Oh, you mean this one?
What a couple of idiots.
You guys have any ideas about dinner?
Bipe me!
Fine.
No food for you.
I better check to see how
that Skull soup is doing.
I wonder if I could use
the feathers as a gorge.
That could be interesting.
Huh?
Huh, there's something
strange with that ship.
I know that song!
N-Nuffy! Zoro! What happened?
Why are you bleeding? Nami!
Oh no! Are you all right?
Doctor!
You're the doctor!
So check them out already! Ow! Right!
So, what happened to you guys?
It looks like you were mauled
by a pack of rabid wolves.
It was pirates but we're okay
just some scratches yeah you
guys seem to be okay with
everything but I certainly am not
what's wrong with you two you
are men right when someone
provokes you the only logical
response would be to pull their
faces and wipe out the blood
with their friends faces or
better yet you should just blow
up the entire annoying down
what happened to all that
pacifist talk shut up zoro what's
fast is past we're not talking
about ancient history here Hey,
why is she in such a bad mood?
She didn't get a single scratch on her.
Huh, it's me.
Oh, yeah!
Did you get any information
about Sky Island?
Sky Island?
Does it even matter anymore?
All I did was say the word Sky
Island, and they all laughed at me!
What the heck was so funny
about me saying that?!
Bunch of jerks!
I am the Ketchup Star!
It sounds like I missed out on some
excitement here. How's everyone doing?
Robin!
Welcome back, my love!
I can draw a bath and prepare a fruit
plate for you if you're interested!
Hey there, Robin.
Where have you been all day, huh?
Well, I went shopping for clothes and
found some information on Skypiea.
That's right!
You're the one who brought it up!
I was made to look like an
idiot thanks to your big mouth!
Trust me!
If this place turns out to not exist,
I'll throw you overboard
with rocks in your pockets!
Robin, I'd kinda keep my
distance if I were you.
At least for the next two hours.
Just don't rock the boat,
know what I'm saying?
Here you go, Captain?
Ooh, thanks, Robin!
Looks like a normal map.
So what's the big deal?
It's this island.
On the left side is Mocktown,
which is where we are now.
And if you look on the other side,
you'll see an X on the coast.
Supposedly,
a man lives there that was banished from
this town because he didn't blend in.
Didn't blend in?
His name is Mont Blanc Cricket
Apparently, Mr.
Cricket talked about his dreams too much
Sounds like you have something in common.
Captain, all undersea
preparations are operational!
Microphone ready.
Excellent, initiate the search, sonar?
Number 27!
Sonar response confirmed!
We detected a school
of fish at 9 o 'clock!
Judging from their speed,
we're looking at sorry fish!
Yeah!
Time for a fish fry!
Diver 4 here, sonar response confirmed.
A small sailing vessel has
been detected on the surface.
Excuse me, a vessel?
Determine the exact
direction it's traveling.
It's dead ahead, sir.
Twelve o 'clock.
It's already close enough
for visual contact?
Cancel the search and
return to the ship at once.
Well, it didn't take us long
to run into something weird.
Do you think it's that same
salvage boat from before?
Or...
Nah, it might look like a similar
ship, but it's not Mashida's group.
Yeah, because Chopper and
I saw those guys, right?
Right, we saw them docking.
Turns out they ported Mocktown, the
same as most ships in these waters.
They're greedy slime,
just like all the others.
You know, those guys better hope
we don't run into them again.
Hey, hey, hey, you guys!
Shut your traps and pay attention!
Can you believe I actually got all
worked up wondering who you people were?
Your face looks weird.
What species are you?
I'm human, moron!
Are you telling us you
don't know who Shoujo is?
He's only the captain
of the Shoujo pirates
and the world's leader in undersea search.
I wouldn't make our boss
angry if I were you.
Hey, now, now, hold on.
Hmm.
It looks like we're in
the same profession.
Were you aware that Crocodile, who is
one of the seven warlords of the sea,
was defeated recently?
When you consider my dominating abilities,
that open spot is as good as mine.
I've been doing my best to stay patient,
but lately the anticipation
has gotten the best of me.
So your goal is to become one of
the seven warlords of the sea?
Didn't I just say that?
In any case, you're
obviously not a threat to me,
so let's get to know
each other personally.
I'll start.
Did you know I haven't had
my haircut in my entire life?
That's over 25 years.
You're impressed and jealous. Admit it.
That's lame.
How dare you?
Watch your mouth, kid.
Settle down, my faithful divers.
I'm not gonna let these foul-mouthed
punks get away with insulting me.
Take this to heart.
Sail through the tunnel that
is my rage and you'll be
met by a sea of blood from
which you'll never escape.
Yeah, whatever. Move aside.
We have places to go and people to meet.
You just don't get it, do you?
This is my turf, and if you want to
pass, you either pay the toll or be sunk.
Get it?
What's this guy mean by his turf?
He's starting to sound like
our old friend Mashida.
Huh?
Mashida said stuff like that?
What? Mashida?
What about Mashida?
If you must know, we kicked his butt
off our boat, but we didn't think...
You what?
Kicked him?
Easy, boss.
How dare you lay a hand on my
brother, my own flesh and blood!
Sure we threw him off our
boat, but I bet he's alive.
Havoc sonar!
The ship!
So, what are they doing?
Who knows, but it's amazing.
He's destroying his own
ship with his voice.
Back to work, everyone.
Let's use this to our advantage and
put some distance between us and them.
Great idea!
Look, Nami's not a demon anymore. Really?
Well, I hope she be calmer after
letting off all that steam earlier.
Luffy, we've got trouble!
This isn't good.
The waves are moving
faster than I thought.
Oh, great!
The ship's starting to break apart right
where I made all those repairs today!
Ah!
She's beat up enough already!
If we stay here any longer,
we'll start taking on water!
Full speed ahead!
We need to get out of this voice's range!
I'm telling you, it was
the strangest thing.
This gorgeous woman walks in.
I mean, she was a knockout.
She comes up to me and leans
over the table and says,
Tell me where this man
named Cricket lives.
Sounds like a bold woman. Bold?
No, she was more like a maniac.
All of a sudden,
these hands started popping out from her
body and knocking out
everyone in the joint.
I'm telling you, it really
messed with my head.
Ha!
I'm confused.
What does tearing up the bar
have to do with old man Cricket?
The sea around here is the unofficial
turf of those monkey brothers.
But if someone actually wants to have
something to do with that geezer,
then they must have caught
some of his own stupidity.
No one wants that.
I bet you what that lady's really
after is his gold. His gold?
I heard they found some recently.
Yeah? Where at?
Hey, guys!
Bellamy!
What did you just say about gold?
This old man that goes by crickets.
I'd like to set up a meeting with him.
What do you know of him?